<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://oopspatty.github.io</id>
    <title>Patty&apos;s Portfolio</title>
    <updated>2020-02-06T14:59:34.834Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://oopspatty.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://oopspatty.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>A UX pilot, occasionally an illustrator. 
&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Currently @Accenture SH Liquid Studio designing friendly artificial intelligence</subtitle>
    <logo>https://oopspatty.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://oopspatty.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2020, Patty&apos;s Portfolio</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SKODA CHINA Customer Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://oopspatty.github.io/post/skoda-china-cj</id>
        <link href="https://oopspatty.github.io/post/skoda-china-cj">
        </link>
        <updated>2019-08-28T07:33:19.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In order to improve auto sales decline and low brand recognition in China, VW SKODA delegated Accenture to explore and optimize the experience of China Customer Journey.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1580194384355.png" alt="skoda-personas" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>Starting from customer-centric service, we defined several typical <strong>architypes</strong> via in-depth interview and research, and depicted corresponding <strong>customer journey AS-IS</strong> to reflect their experience, needs and expectations.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1580999137336.jpg" alt="skoda-cj-asis" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>In addition, we also organized an <strong>innovation workshop</strong> that involved stakeholders from clients and customers, to jointly create the upgraded products and service offerings, then successfully envisioned China <strong>Customer Journey To-Bes</strong>. Tangible items delivered to VW SKODA include a backlog of service offerings and concepts, Customer Journey As-Ises and To-Bes for four architypes, and a project report.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1580194402169.png" alt="skoda-workshop" loading="lazy"></figure>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="4"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579527484759.jpg" alt="skoda-cj-tobe" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>In Accenture, we adhere to the value proposition of our clients, help Global Brands better understand their customers in local markets, enhance the brand loyalty, and facilitate digital transformation and experience optimization.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[40 Days to Unlock Staff's Innovation Potential]]></title>
        <id>https://oopspatty.github.io/post/bjmtr</id>
        <link href="https://oopspatty.github.io/post/bjmtr">
        </link>
        <updated>2019-04-30T13:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As a leading service provider of urban rail transit in China, the Beijing Mass Transit Railway (Aka BJ-MTR) looks for new approaches that would make the operation task management more agile, creative and innovative in their digital transformation. Thus, BJ-MTR selected Accenture Greater China to rapidly innovate disruptive and digital services on task management for front-stage staff using Design Thinking and a lean start-up approach.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579419653406.PNG" alt="Liquid Studio's Ambition" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>Accenture is helping BJ-MTR build the relevant knowledge, skill set, and organizational structure to ideate, develop, and implement customer-relevant <strong>minimum lovable product</strong> in a short timeframe — or fail fast.<br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="chapter-1-understand-our-people-interviewworkshop">Chapter 1. Understand our people (Interview+Workshop)</h1>
<p><strong>If you want to make digital transformation, you have to know what to motivate.</strong></p>
<p>No matter an enterprise product or a consumer product, the behaviors of the end-users are the foremost to be understood. In this circumstance, the front-stage working staff are the ones we need to empathize.</p>
<p>And of course, knowing better about the biz workflow. Accenture team conducted the interviews with different roles for the different workflows, for better understanding the people’s needs and motivations, and the business process As-Is as well.<br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579421393861.JPG" alt="BJ-mtr-workshop-1" loading="lazy"><br>
After getting first-hand information, Accenture organized a two-day Design Thinking Workshop, which involved the BJ-MTR people from Managing, Operation, IT and front-stage crew and the designers, scrum masters and tech experts from Accenture,  analyzing the pain-point, biz requirements, human needs, while potential technical innovation opportunities.<br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579419995299.JPG" alt="BJ-mtr-workshop" loading="lazy"></p>
<h1 id="chapter-2-get-your-hands-dirty-shadowing">Chapter 2. Get your hands dirty (shadowing)</h1>
<p><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579420079442.jpeg" alt="BJ-mtr-shadowing-1" loading="lazy"><br>
For defining the clear opportunities of digitalization, designers from ACN delivered a shadowing research to put themselves into staff’s shoes - observing and following their daily working routes, recording the difficulties and pain-points, collecting the measurement criteria for current business workflows, which are the basis of orientation to build a new digital platform.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579420124178.jpeg" alt="BJ-mtr-shadowing-2" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="chapter-3-play-to-consolidate-responsibly-prototyping-test">Chapter 3. Play to consolidate, responsibly (Prototyping &amp; Test)</h1>
<p>We followed Agile to make quick progress. However, the end of design is not to make a beautiful interface, the optimization of a business process is not the destination of a project. <strong>Consolidation in a responsible way is an alchemy stone of the assumption trial, whether it is feasible, desirable and achieve goal or not.</strong><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579420517895.PNG" alt="BJ-mtr-test-1" loading="lazy"><br>
In order to better simulate the prototype in an assumed scenarios, the ACN team invited different staff to carry out interface evaluation on the paper prototype from their own perspectives in the task. We also made clickable interactive prototypes for the end users to experience. During the experience prototype, the Think-Out-Loud approach allowed them to express their opinions, while these voices encouraged each other participants to speak out and inspired the design team as well.<br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579420530132.PNG" alt="BJ-mtr-test-2" loading="lazy"></p>
<h1 id="chapter-4-the-outcome">Chapter 4. The outcome</h1>
<p>The people involved initiated innovation change for BJ-MTR staff that allowed them to understand and learn how to innovate in a design-thinking-led way. Accenture team also created a framework for a repeatable innovation practice at BJ-MTR over the 3 courses of 2-week sprints - Stay agile and continuously iteration, while scene expansion and data accumulation.</p>
<p>Another outcome was design doing. Accenture design team delivered a tangible product with transparency in information and processes, leading to trust across departments,  efficiency and pleasure brought by digital convenience. Tangible items delivered to BJ-MTR include a report of user experience evaluation, demos for different roles and workflows, a high-fidelity interactive prototype based on the selected workflows.<br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579421343554.JPG" alt="BJ-mtr-final" loading="lazy"></p>
<h1 id="chapter-x-continuous-going">Chapter X. Continuous Going</h1>
<p>The minimum lovable service, moved forward with Digital Product Creation for task management, into the Deliver phases. There, Accenture’s delivery team will involve and start to architect through the prioritized product backlog to develop the system services. This will be followed by a release pilot.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings >w< A message for you~]]></title>
        <id>https://oopspatty.github.io/post/about</id>
        <link href="https://oopspatty.github.io/post/about">
        </link>
        <updated>2019-01-25T11:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="nice-to-meet-you"><strong>Nice to meet you!</strong></h2>
<p>Welcome to my little bumbling world 😆</p>
<p>I am an <strong>empathy-driven experience design</strong> pilot, and currently diving into hi-tech realm exploring the possibility of <strong>Artificial Intelligence</strong> to levitate the human's life and business at <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/capability-rapid-application-development-studio">Accenture Shanghai Liquid Studio</a>. During my spare time, I love roaming around the world, seeking and capturing the little tiny beautiful things.</p>
<p>Let's chat more if you share common interests and faith with me: patriciawangtl@gmail.com. Also you can find me via my <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/patty-tiaoling-wang/">LinkedIn</a>, <a href="https://www.behance.net/oopspatty">Behance</a> and <a href="http://www.instagram.com/oopspatty">Instagram</a> to see what I am moving forward.😆😆</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1580201913320.png" alt="PattyImage" loading="lazy"></figure>
<br>
<p><strong>Proudly served:</strong><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1580206992674.png" alt="logos" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital illustration - Be with you]]></title>
        <id>https://oopspatty.github.io/post/Be-with-you</id>
        <link href="https://oopspatty.github.io/post/Be-with-you">
        </link>
        <updated>2018-06-27T06:47:06.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Using digital illustration to record the nature of moment among the relationships for my surrounding loved ones. The theme of this collection is <strong>Be with You</strong>.</p>
<p><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579332024753.PNG" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579332032902.PNG" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579332039568.PNG" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579332047936.PNG" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579332058188.PNG" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579332052805.PNG" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[StoryPot - Road to Know Alzheimer's Disease]]></title>
        <id>https://oopspatty.github.io/post/storypot</id>
        <link href="https://oopspatty.github.io/post/storypot">
        </link>
        <updated>2018-06-12T10:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a personal project supporting my graduate thesis - Research on current public perception of Alzheimer’s disease among Chinese young generations. The research was proudly to be appreciated by Alzheimer's Association, Greater Cincinnati Chapter.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579451728046.png" alt="1-problem" loading="lazy"></figure>
<hr>
<h1 id="insiders-vs-outsiders">INSIDERS vs OUTSIDERS</h1>
<p>During my journey of research, people can be generally categorized as two groups based on that if they have the experience and prior knowledge about Alzheimer's disease or not.<br>
<strong>Alzheimer's Insiders</strong> - People who have/had relatives with Alzheimer's.<br>
<strong>Alzheimer's Outsiders</strong> - People who might not have a relative with Alzheimer's YET.<br>
<br><br>
There is, however, no actual boundary between two groups of people, for instance, an individual who recently find his/her family member showing symptoms of Alzheimer's or the senior loved ones who are lately diagnosed with Alzheimer's. And, the voice from the insiders can reliably guide the outsiders to know better about the disease even what next steps to leap as long as it occurs.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579451825875.png" alt="2-assumption" loading="lazy"></figure>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579451868264.png" alt="3-requested features" loading="lazy"></figure>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="4"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579451899668.png" alt="4-proposal" loading="lazy"></figure>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="5"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579451928020.png" alt="5-cover" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579451951724.png" alt="6-system map" loading="lazy"><br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="strategy-concept">STRATEGY &amp; CONCEPT</h1>
<p><a href="https://etd.ohiolink.edu/pg_10?::NO:10:P10_ETD_SUBID:162857">A research which referred to an existing public perception of Alzheimer’s disease in China</a> at the beginning of this project.  Studies on reasons, personas, experience map of delivering caregiving service are in the following slides.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="6"><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579452004048.jpg" alt="7-research" loading="lazy"></figure>
<p>Based on the research findings, information architecture, wireframes, user flow and storyboard for the whole digital experience followed.<br>
<br><br>
Two digital experience — mobile application for communication and service searching &amp; website for knowledge promotion — are proposed to boost the public awareness on Alzheimer’s disease and minimize the societal-isolation that caused by the disease.<br>
<br></p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c66e9c3668914.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c66e9c3668914.jpg" alt="8.jpg" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c66e0c4b95999.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c66e0c4b95999.jpg" alt="9.jpg" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="1build-up-community-with-approachable-knowledge-storypotorg">1.Build up community with approachable knowledge - StoryPot.org</h1>
<p>The appearance of website, was structured into a series of questions with supportive encyclopedia about Alzheimer’s which build a general understanding for an engaging experience on the users.<br>
The end of survey will assess the participants' knowledge level and lead them to consider about the next steps.<br>
<br></p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="7"><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d0380feac03f34934.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d0380feac03f34934.png" alt="19.png" loading="lazy"></a></figure>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037f5e77a6382031.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037f5e77a6382031.png" alt="17.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037f5e71a2c62251.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037f5e71a2c62251.png" alt="18.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="2-speak-listen-and-collaborate">2. Speak, Listen and Collaborate</h1>
<p>The mobile application is designed to increase the accessibility of information about Alzheimer's disease to eliminate the social isolation.<br>
<br><br>
It is a user backend to connect the people who are already/potentially affected by the Alzheimer's, like the families, professionals, volunteers, etc. With this approach, all the communities can reach the authentic stories and experience about the Alzheimer's. Meanwhile, the users can easily locate, engage and manage related campaigns and service to support themselves when necessary.</p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037878c04a969125.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037878c04a969125.png" alt="10.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<h2 id="social-engagement">Social Engagement</h2>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Stories, functioning as the catalyst to open the heart of both Alzheimer's affected persons and Alzheimer's-resisted groups, can also prompt the elimination of social isolations.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Communication on the platform increase the efficiency of information accessibility, expand the networking and introduce more possibilities to problem-solving.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Bringing the resources of related campaigns, organization and services to satisfy the offline needs.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c6725d4b72718.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c6725d4b72718.png" alt="11.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c65deeb937404.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c65deeb937404.png" alt="12.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c66b086578748.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c66b086578748.png" alt="13.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c676271142977.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c676271142977.jpg" alt="14.jpg" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c66ee52f89364.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037c66ee52f89364.png" alt="15.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037f5f815e340488.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d037f5f815e340488.png" alt="16.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<iframe src="//invis.io/YCGYEZ54EQF" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen style="margin:0px auto;display:block;width:442px;height:935px;" class="embed-content"></iframe>
<br>
<hr>
<h1 id="reflection">Reflection</h1>
<p>My original intention is to design a simply communicative platform to solve the understanding issue for the people who are both affected by the disease and the non-sufferers, particularly for Chinese communities - most of who know little about it - and both groups are socially separated by the disease. That the StoryPot app came to my mind to resolve the severity of misunderstanding and miscommunication. As my research went deeper, however, I found the psychological rejection and lack of understanding prohibit the public to access to the disease-related information. Further as I researched, how to catch the public's attention to the disease is also as crucial as a prerequisite for those people who know little about the disease. Thus, here comes the idea of StoryPot.org.<br>
<br></p>
<p>Improving the lives of people who are affected by the Alzheimer's disease is a life-long task. To prepare for the future in advance with generations and generations bonding is the key to end it.</p>
<h1 id="follow-up">FOLLOW UP</h1>
<p>In terms of time limitation and explosion of existing social networking, the StoryPot App is looking for a better way to launch. However, the great news is, the clinicians (who I interviewed during the research stage) and I built a temporary chatting group on the most popular SNS in China. Until April 2018, 78 persons (including young individuals and family members) have been in this group and share all the info about Alzheimer's from time to time, of course there are much more opportunities to propagandize disease-related events. Another notable news is, the StoryPot.org is on the list of construction.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goblin App - Your Mood Recorder & Guidance]]></title>
        <id>https://oopspatty.github.io/post/goblin-app</id>
        <link href="https://oopspatty.github.io/post/goblin-app">
        </link>
        <updated>2017-12-08T12:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d038e1ad4e1070998.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d038e1ad4e1070998.png" alt="2.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d038e1b3990375273.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d038e1b3990375273.jpg" alt="3.jpg" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d038e1bb38e843058.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d038e1bb38e843058.jpg" alt="4.jpg" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d038e1c0b75278655.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d038e1c0b75278655.png" alt="5.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d038e1bd846761660.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/14/5d038e1bd846761660.png" alt="1.png" loading="lazy"></a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-reflection from my Internship]]></title>
        <id>https://oopspatty.github.io/post/internship</id>
        <link href="https://oopspatty.github.io/post/internship">
        </link>
        <updated>2017-08-30T14:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In summer 2017, I had my internship at the design consultancy - Live Well Collaborative. It was a splendid time with understanding and growing-up. Working with incredible and talented people, meeting collaborators of totally different backgrounds, I had a pleasure of learning, designing and crafting experience in a very complicated world. I worked with two distinctive client groups and was in charge of two projects — they were extremely different —</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>One was working with a local senior living facility, to redesign the emergency exit door context for residents with dementia there, which is a system design project, mostly on the basis of design thinking, and finally we came out a comprehensive and systematic solution.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The other one was serving Cincinnati Children's Hospital for two tasks — devising a new Oncology Handbook and releasing the 1-2-3 initiative device. This project led me into printing world together with elevating my practical engineering skills, which I developed in my undergraduate time, to create a real objective for real needs. It can be said that these tasks were bitter-sweet challenges and affirmation for my all-round ability.<br>
<br></p>
</li>
</ul>
<h1 id="some-highlights-of-internship">Some highlights of internship</h1>
<ul>
<li>Learned new research methods and applied them into practices.</li>
<li>My tasks covered the whole process of projects from scratch —— conducting user-centered research, contributing ideas, mockup-making, user-testing and refinement.</li>
<li>All of projects are utility-considered, which is different from my academic projects.</li>
<li>Communicating and exchanging some ideas between teams in spare time, led me felt mind-opening and enriched myself from others' perspectives.</li>
<li>Working in Live Well Collaborative also shaped me a systematic design approach, and this approach would definitely help me as well in my design career:</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce404e6149b669660.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce404e6149b669660.png" alt="Design Process" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="1-understanding-the-essence-of-communication">1. Understanding the essence of communication</h1>
<p>When starting a project, usually we set our target groups well, and begin our research —— interviewing one by one, collecting enough data and summarizing, then directly diving into design practice, ending up with beautiful slides to present. BUT, is it so smooth to achieve our goal in reality ?</p>
<p>During my internship, communication is everywhere and you have to initiative to iterate your design method. In the project Design for Dementia, in fact, my team was not allowed to directly interview the residents with dementia. However, we interacted with stakeholders from nurses, serving staff, programers even directors. We exchanged our ideas as much as we can, of course including observation, making any effort to understand our target users and where the exact pain-points lie. In the validation stage, we further invited non-involved co-workers to test our prototypes, which in turn gave us precious feedback to iterate our work. <strong>Honestly, listening carefully to the voice from clients and stakeholders would teach you, talking breezily with other people would surprise you.</strong> <br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="2-problem-identification-plays-important-role">2. Problem identification plays important role</h1>
<p>For design beginner, even for some of our experienced colleagues, the circumstance of putting ourselves into delivering a solution is usual, sometimes it happened unconsciously because it's easy and clear. This unpleasant situation also bothered me before, in this case, how can we transform the way we think becomes vital.<br>
<br></p>
<p>Another example of the project Design for Dementia, we were firstly tasked to redesign the emergency exit doors because they posed a security threat to the demented residents. But why security doors were a threat? Are they really the problem we need to resolve? Embracing with such questions, we did a field trip, analyzed the context even looked up some research about elderly behaviors. One of our findings came out that the emergency door attracted residents to explore because, to some extend, they were forbidden to go outside by the staff for the personal safety consideration! How paradoxical the reason it is, right? Knowing that key info, our team just changed the way we think of the problem —— why don't we try to make this problem become a problem-solving? That's what leading us came out a partial solution in our solution system. (To see more details about the project, click here!)<br>
<br></p>
<p>It is common to get lost while doing research and trying to jump to the solution. But <strong>the problem identification and exploration can lead you to the place that you never be even you never realize, also bring you unexpected growth that can affect your whole life.</strong> <br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="3-always-be-curious-not-judgmental">3. Always be curious, not judgmental.</h1>
<p>This is my motto, I hope it can also enlighten you a little bit. Preconceived ideas will always play a decisive role, but as a designer, embracing ambiguity and maintain curious leads you to open your mind.</p>
<p>When doing the project Oncology Books, me and my co-work came up with several creative ideas for patients, abandoning traditional book style which we thought it's out-of-date. However, gaining feedbacks from medical staff and participants, a simple-to-use handbook with our innovative elements became the final design — Not changing users behaviors while bringing much convenience for users to achieve the goal — which guarantee the useful and feasible features for both sides.</p>
<p>It's really frustrated sometimes when your solution was not selected as the final one. But this is not a bad end, right? See this situation in a different way: Is the solution a final desicive one? Is there any problem that the solution did not cover? Does the solution really solve the main problem that bothering your client? Can you learn something new from the selected solution?<br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="4-continuity">4. Continuity</h1>
<p>I left this part as my ending part. Not just because learning is a life-long task, but also design is dynamic and continuous to work long and prosper. Design is not a math question that the answer is one-time validated, it could be being iterative forever, and get ready for that there is always a better design solution on the way.</p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce40569556c519598.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce40569556c519598.jpg" alt="Photo of Family Live Well Collaborative.jpg" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<small>Commemoration after final presentation in Live Well Collaborative. Photo credits to Live Well Collaborative.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenwood - System Design for Senior Living Facility]]></title>
        <id>https://oopspatty.github.io/post/kenwood</id>
        <link href="https://oopspatty.github.io/post/kenwood">
        </link>
        <updated>2017-08-11T13:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Now you are reading a system design story based on design thinking that I was interning in 2017 at <a href="http://livewellcollaborative.org">Live Well Collaborative</a>. Collaborated with a local senior living facility, The Kenwood by Senior Star, we were asked to redefine the emergency exit door environment for the independent-living senior residents with dementia.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce402f35f9c380124.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce402f35f9c380124.png" alt="Kenwood_floor_plan" loading="lazy"></a></figure>
<p>The Kenwood by Senior Star is proud to serve as a valuable senior residential assisted living resource for all Cincinnati families. In the second floor of care building lives movable demented residents. Due to <strong>overworked staff</strong>, taking care of the demented residents becomes more challenged. Plus the <strong>complicated interior environment</strong>, that the residents with dementia tend to easily roam around and come through the emergency exit door lead <strong>potential risks</strong> on the innocent residents.</p>
<br>
<h1 id="research-strategy">RESEARCH STRATEGY</h1>
<p>Start with benchmarking the existing products and services for demented persons, interviews with working staff and observation on residents were soon organized to understand what the problem is. A dementia-affected resident's journey was illustrated to envision where the needs lie and where the opportunities are located.</p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce405e61ecf241598.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce405e61ecf241598.png" alt="Kenwood_benchamarking" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/22/5ce42189907bb74033.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/22/5ce42189907bb74033.png" alt="Kenwood_stakeholder_map_n_value_flow" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce405e6afd1291464.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce405e6afd1291464.jpg" alt="Kenwood_persona&amp;xMap" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<em>Experience map color palette inspired by Florencia Pagano.</em><br>
<br></p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce40626af14668724.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce40626af14668724.png" alt="Kenwood_Insight" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="safety-with-humanity">SAFETY WITH HUMANITY</h1>
<p>Instead of depriving the freedom of residents, we attempted to innovate a desired relationship between residents and staff. Therefore, creating a living environment with remained dignity and security is the goal of this project.<br>
<br></p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce406d388b8672211.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce406d388b8672211.png" alt="Kenwood_transformation" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="solution-system">SOLUTION SYSTEM</h1>
<p>Four concept directions below came out based on the research findings. After several rounds of iterations and user-testing with our clients, we came up with a final integrated solution system based on the four design directions.<br>
<br></p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce406d38ebcb97919.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce406d38ebcb97919.jpg" alt="Kenwood_Directions" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce406d53d94225757.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce406d53d94225757.jpg" alt="Kenwood_SoultionSystem" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="co-design">CO-DESIGN</h1>
<p>10 more stakeholders were invited from the Kenwood to test the major solutions including art boxes, do stations and false window. Further, we invited peripheral volunteers to tested prototypes with sensory blockers to simulate a resident’s experience and gain new perspectives.<br>
<br></p>
<p><strong>All the final prototypes have been put into formal use in The Kenwood since August, 2017.</strong> The “outdoor room” is on the plan of construction.<br>
<br></p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce406d440e9f13454.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce406d440e9f13454.jpg" alt="Kenwood_Refine" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce4081105d0439485.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce4081105d0439485.png" alt="Kenwood_Feedback" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="future-opportunities">FUTURE OPPORTUNITIES</h1>
<p>Potential works need to think about in the future to improve the experiences of residents and their loved ones even all of working staff.<br>
<br></p>
<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/22/5ce422f17a49649567.jpg"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/22/5ce422f17a49649567.jpg" alt="Kenwood_Future" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<br></p>
<h1 id="reflection">REFLECTION</h1>
<p>This project gave me a valuable opportunity to solve the problem with user-centered design from very beginning to delivery: identification, research, design and future consideration.</p>
<p>When designing a product or service, one straightforward way is to interact with target users. However, for some special reasons, interviewing <strong>stakeholders bring great insights as well</strong>, particularly in the situation that hard to approach to the target users for designer (so did we in this project).</p>
<p>Additionally, this system design project also taught me that the significance of an integrated solution system to solve a problem. Different from other projects, it gave me more official constraints and challenges but also left me more space to design around.</p>
<p>Lastly, this project led me to deep thought about design for human's future well-being.</p>
<p><strong>Design could be commercial, theoretical or practical, but design should be meaningful and thoughtful.</strong></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charli & Mollie - Robotics Design for Boeing]]></title>
        <id>https://oopspatty.github.io/post/robotics-for-boeing</id>
        <link href="https://oopspatty.github.io/post/robotics-for-boeing">
        </link>
        <updated>2017-04-28T15:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce403aa5b91864882.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce403aa5b91864882.png" alt="Charli.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce403e0c13a986557.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce403e0c13a986557.png" alt="Charli_Medical_Feature.png" loading="lazy"></a><br>
<a href="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce4043730a5197032.png"><img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/21/5ce4043730a5197032.png" alt="Mollie.png" loading="lazy"></a></p>
<p>This project was sponsored by Boeing Company collaborated with Live Well Collaborative.  <a href="http://livewellcollaborative.org/cabin-bot">The cabin bot Charli has proudly became patent filing since January 2018. </a> If you are interested in this project, DM me and I am more than happy to share further details with you.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[「Shin-shin」-Build up your inner Heroine ]]></title>
        <id>https://oopspatty.github.io/post/shinshin</id>
        <link href="https://oopspatty.github.io/post/shinshin">
        </link>
        <updated>2016-12-05T06:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579330790868.jpg" alt="01-background for this project" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579330805898.jpg" alt="02-our persona" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331201243.jpg" alt="03-observation" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331212406.jpg" alt="04-in-depth interview" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331233678.jpg" alt="05-infinity map" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331251631.jpg" alt="06" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331262664.jpg" alt="07-design goal" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331278150.jpg" alt="08-main tasks" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331300688.jpg" alt="09-wireframes" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331318674.jpg" alt="10-prototype test" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331337694.jpg" alt="11-features" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331353144.jpg" alt="12-hi-fi" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://oopspatty.github.io/post-images/1579331396251.jpg" alt="14-final ui-2" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>